It's the ultimate form of self-transformation.
The ultimate manifestation of undying passion.
A form of art, where the body is a
canvas to express the artist's devotion...
...which hundreds of thousands admire and pursue.
This is a story...
A story about young women who cosplay...
...and the love and passion they share.
Senpai...
Make me look cute, okay?
New Student from Another Dimension
Club Building A
Manga Club
Liliel!
No, you can't die!
The Ashford Chronicles
That scene always hits so hard.
I have zero interest in 3D girls.
I'm a second-year in high school,
and I already know I'll never be interested.
good luck
ME (8)
My mom abandoned me to be with some guy.
In grade school, I asked out the girl I liked,
only to be bullied for being a "creep."
The girls in my class all call me a gross otaku.
Ew, barf.
But I couldn't give a damn about that,
and here's why!
There's an angel waiting for me,
just one dimension away!
Ashford-sama!
My waifu, Liliel.
She's sweet and pure,
and only has eyes for the main character.
She's so in love she dies for him
and comes back as an angel!
Know any girls like that in real life?
I didn't think so!
That's why she's perfect!
Club Building
New Members Welcome!!
All the other club members did, too,
but they graduated last year.
Excuse me! Sorry, coming through!
That's fine, though,
'cause 3D girls will never bother me in here.
Manga Club
H-hello?
Are you taking new members?
A 3D girl?!
I'm Ririsa Amano.
I'm a first year, and I really love manga!
Yeah, I bet she only likes shoujo bullcrap!
This club is for ass and titties,
and the guys who love 'em!
No way am I letting some girl
ruin my secret sexy sanctuary!
I'll come up with some excuse
to get her out of here...
These are so cute!
Jackpot!
Those aren't your baby sister's dolls, no, ma'am!
That's a limited-edition strippable figurine!
Now she'll get it.
She'll know she doesn't belong here.
I mean, it's not bad...
This figurine's based on art by a hentai manga-ka
from the fifth anniversary booklet, right?
How'd you know that?!
The face is cute and the costume looks great,
but why'd they give her
boring white panties?
Obviously they weren't visible
in the original design,
but if I were Liliel,
I would've gone with black lace.
I mean...
That would've made her look so much sexier.
She's so right!
Wait, why am I agreeing with her?!
Like yeah, she's right, but...
I'm so sorry!
We literally just met and I'm being all weird...
Oh, nah...
I shouldn't judge her panties.
Everyone's got their own style,
and there's a style for everyone!
That's not why I'm weirded out.
I-I didn't think girls could even be into this stuff.
I am!
I've always been into cute and sexy characters.
I-I know, it's weird, right?
I-it's not weird!
Really?!
Honestly, it means we've got
something in common.
I mean, it seems like you know
a lot about Liliel.
Yes!
There's no one who loves her more than me!
Y-yeah, right!
She's every man's fantasy
rolled into one perfect package!
What would a girl know about that?
Try me!
I've always liked heroines
designed for a male audience!
I kinda self-insert into them!
They might be fictional, but all the things
boys like about them are real!
Liliel is cute, and sexy,
and is always turning heads...
She's a little awkward,
but she wears her heart on her sleeve,
and everyone loves her!
That's why I fell in love with her, too!
And not just that...
I want to BE Liliel!
You want to WHAT?!
I never thought I'd meet someone
who loved Liliel as much as I do!
But she's still one dimension too many!
Huh?
That's the old movie!
You've seen the old movie, too?!
The team behind the legendary OVA
reunited to create another masterpiece!
Taniguchi's script brought Liliel
into the spotlight for the first time!
Nakamura's gorgeous sakuga!
It's so smooth!
I know!
And watch this effect!
Here comes that famous scene!
Liliel!
Dammit, she's the perfect Liliel fan!
Why does she have to be a girl?!
I could have another club member
to gush over Liliel with...
I'd kill for that!
But she's still 3D!
Hey!
Senpai, could you help me with something?
With what?
There's this weird hobby I'm into...
I've never told anyone about it, so...
So I'm really worried it'll weird you out.
You're sorely mistaken!
You're quoting Ash-sama from Episode 13!
Wow, you got that?
You think I'd get weirded out by that?
Me, Okumura?
A real otaku NEVER judges
someone by the things they love!
That love, that passion, is our heart and soul!
That is what makes us otaku!
My senpai told me that once,
and now I get to tell her!
Wait, why am I being so supportive?!
Wasn't I trying to get rid of her?!
Thank goodness!
G-give me a sec.
Huh?
Can I show you something?
This is my collection.
Are these DVDs?
Wait, is this porn?
Milky
Succubus
No, it's cosplay...
They're called cosroms.
They're collections of cosplay photos and videos.
I want to make one of my own!
Huh?
Wait...
WHAT?!
Manga
Club
Milky Succubus
So you wanna do this? Wear this?
Um, didn't you just say you wouldn't judge?
R-right, of course not! This is cool.
You're gonna let people see this, though?
Ever since I was a kid,
I've loved the costumes manga characters wear.
I'd always picture myself wearing them,
especially if they were cute and sexy.
I figured most people would look down on me,
so I kept it a secret for a long time.
But, then...
I went to my first in-person event.
Whoa, I can't believe they're wearing that in public...
And there are so many other women here to see them!
I'm such a huge fan!
Your last ROM was so hot!
I know, right?!
I really focused on my ass for this new one.
So it's okay for girls to
talk about this stuff, too...
Hey, sweetie, how old are you?
Huh?
This is a softcore event, so come back
when you're in high school, mmkay?
That's when I realized...
It's awesome when people can openly
and proudly pursue their passions!
When no one can stop them
from doing what they love,
no matter what they say!
So I'm gonna be proud of what I like
and make a cosrom with Liliel!
With Liliel?
Right.
Forgive me, I did say I wouldn't judge.
It's okay!
Thank you for taking me so seriously!
What did you need help with?
Oh, right!
Well, uh...
If you let me join the club...
Will you take pictures of me?!
What?! Why me?!
Usually you'd find a photographer online,
but I dunno about being alone with a stranger...
Yeah, that makes sense.
Still, I barely know how to use a camera.
That's fine! I'm totally new to this, too!
All we need is passion!
I'd rather take pictures with someone
who shares my love for Liliel, too.
We do share that...
I knew I wanted to make my own ROM
once I started high school.
EXTRACURRICULAR CLUB GUIDE
When I came here to take the entry exam,
I saw this room...
Wait a sec! That's a Liliel poster!
Liliel!
I felt like fate was calling me here!
Think I'm ready to die now...
You're such a huge Liliel fan,
and you heard me out and took me seriously.
I feel like I can trust you with this!
So... can I join?
If I let her join...
For real, dude?
Okay.
Cosplay's a big part of the manga world.
Our club would love to have an otaku like you.
Your cosplay plans can be part of
our sanctioned club activities!
Really?!
And you won't have to worry about me.
Liliel is my waifu,
3D women don't affect me
or attract me in the slightest.
Wear all the sexy outfits you want,
I guarantee you I won't feel a thing for you!
You're a legend! An otaku legend!
Please, you flatter me.
This is fine. Her gender aside...
I see now she's a real otaku.
Hell, it sounds like it's gonna be
another great year of being an otaku.
Okay!
Let's get right to it!
Wait, what the hell?!
I figured I should let you see what I have,
so I brought one of my costumes.
And you're gonna put it on here?!
S-sorry, there wasn't a good place to change!
We don't have curtains on our window!
Wait, we can do this!
What the hell is wrong with her?!
Calm down!
I'm freaking out because of how
suddenly that happened!
Not because I'm attracted to 3DPD!
You can look now!
Ashford-sama!
How's that?
S-senpai! Are you okay?!
Y-yeah.
Nope. I am so not okay.
Holy shit. It's her. It's Liliel, in the flesh.
Are you sure?
I went with her standard angel outfit first.
The real Liliel is standing right in front of me.
Well? I made sure all the details were perfect!
Did I slip into the 2D world somehow?
Shit! I gotta snap out of it!
Just calm down!
Oh, right.
I went with these panties.
What do you think?
I mean, they're part of the costume, too,
so it's not like this is anything weird.
Y-y-yep, not weird at all!
You can see her butt all throughout
the battle in Chapter 128,
so I thought of going for a thong,
but I think a bikini cut is
way more in-character for Liliel.
So, what do you think?
I want to hear your opinion!
Yeah. Sure. It's great.
Senpai!
My waifu is 2D... 3D girls are disgusting...
Senpai?
Senpai!
My waifu is 2D... 3D girls are disgusting...
Senpai, are you okay?!
But...
You must be feeling sick! I'm sorry if I made it worse!
2.5D girls are... well...
I can't wait to get started tomorrow, Senpai!
Guess I won't know till I give 'em a try...
Senpai!
Yesterday was a mess.
I can't believe I let her join...
I'm not in love with her, am I?! Me?!
Lusting after a filthy 3D girl?!
I swore I'd be loyal to Liliel forever!
H-hey there, Senpai!
Uh... h-hey, Amano-san.
Oh, you can call me Ririsa,
since I'm your kohai!
Already?!
Okay, Ririsa.
Thanks, Senpai!
Are you watching the OVA?!
Huh? Oh, yeah.
I could never get my hands on it!
Yeah, it's pretty old.
A shame, really, since there are so many
scenes that make it a work of art.
Of course you'd know!
Please, tell me everything!
W-well, if you insist!
Up until now, she's been feeling overwhelmed
by the pressure to help her friends,
but right here, she finally realizes how much
her friends have been helping her, too,
but she doesn't say it out loud!
Really?!
Cause you can see it on her face! See?
Forget flashy lasers or smooth motion,
this attention to detail is godlike animation!
How do you know so much?!
I've done my research.
Wait, senpai...
How is this part of your research?
Wanna see?
Senpai, you're cheating!
Nope, this is all in the game!
Then I'm gonna pick a different fighter next time,
Holy shit! This is so fun!
either Nasu or Gorgon!
I always wanted a cool kohai like this!
I never should've worried about her.
She's the perfect otaku buddy!
Senpai, mind if I try pausing a little?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Yes!
You can see her undies in a few frames!
What is she, a horny thirteen-year-old boy?!
Whenever I see a sexy outfit,
I have to write down all the little details!
Yeah, that makes sense.
I want my cosplays to be
as realistic as possible.
That way, I can bring
each character into real life.
I want people to see my cosplay
and think their favorite character
really exists before them!
I get it now.
That's why I reacted to her...
Senpai!
I need to get into my cosplay, right now!
Can I get changed?!
You're already changing!
C'mon, idiot!
I'm just impressed by how
high-quality her cosplay was!
I am NOT in love with her!
Thanks for being patient!
I am not...
Today, I went with the training outfit
from the Angel Academy spin-off.
Wow, looks good.
What do you need me to do?
Right!
Could you take some pictures of me,
just on your phone?
Sure, but I don't know what I'm doing.
Just let your love for Liliel guide you!
That's not gonna help!
I'll pose here.
You just keep clicking away!
Okay...
ANGEL ACADEMY
Chapter 81
That's the front page from
Chapter 81 of the spin-off!
In real life!
Senpai?
Right, sorry!
She's so cute.
Perfect...
This is so much fun!
I'm gonna try another costume.
Wait, you have more?
All ready!
Whoa, that's her third squad uniform!
Damn, I have no idea what angles
will make her look good,
but this is actually really fun!
How do I look? Can I see?
Sure, here.
These are incredible!
You're awesome, Senpai!
My Liliel looks mega cute!
Guess my passion did guide me.
I knew it would! See this first pose?
It looks just like the art from that chapter!
You can feel my love
for Liliel coming through!
I'm so glad I asked you to help!
This one's good, too!
Damn, she really does love Liliel.
And this one, too! The next few are so cute...
That's why she found the courage to ask me to help.
It's already this late?
I'll change back into my uniform, then.
Okay.
I promised her I'd never feel a thing from her.
There's no going back on that.
She's just the coolest kohai
I could ever ask for.
I'll support her with the purest intentions.
Um, Senpai?
My zipper's kinda stuck.
Could you help me undress?
HELP YOU WHAT?!
HELP YOU WHAT!!?
Just give the zipper a tug!
See, right here?
Um, sure, okay.
Damn, it's really stuck...
Yeah. I made it myself,
so it's probably a little janky-
There!
Hell yeah, I didn't see shit!
Thanks, Senpai...
Lili-
Liliel, are you okay?!
I mean, uh, Ririsa.
I'm okay. Thanks for catching me...
...Ashford-sama.
Very funny, Ririsa!
Sorry, Senpai.
So, uh... Could you let go of me?
Huh?
Sorry, I didn't mean to!
I know.
It's gonna take some time to change,
so feel free to head out without me.
You got it! Okay, bye!
What is wrong with me?!
He's a lot stronger than he looks.
Why's my heart racing so fast?
Something's off...
Am I coming down with a fever?
I'd better take some medicine
when I get home!
Cosplay Group Potential?